<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
To change this license header, choose License Headers in Project Properties.
To change this template file, choose Tools | Templates
and open the template in the editor.
-->


<Warframes>
    <Warframe>
        <Name>Mesa</Name>
        <Abilities>
            <Ability>
                <AName1>Ballistic Battery</AName1>
                <Description1>When activated, this power stores damage caused by guns. 
                    When triggered again, that damage is channeled through the next gunshot.
                </Description1>
            </Ability>
            <Ability>
                <AName2>Shooting Gallery</AName2>
                <Description2>Gives an ally extra damage while jamming the guns of nearby enemies. This power shifts between team members.</Description2>
            </Ability>
            <Ability>
                <AName3>Shatter Shield</AName3>
                <Description3>Envelops Mesa in a barrier of energy, reflecting back incoming bullet damage.</Description3>
            </Ability>
            <Ability>
                <AName4>Peacemaker</AName4>
                <Description4>With intense focus, Mesa draws her Regulator pistols, shooting down her foes in rapid succession.</Description4>
            </Ability>
        </Abilities>
    </Warframe>
    <Warframe>
        <Name>Gara</Name>
        <Abilities>
            <Ability>
                <AName1>Shattered Lash</AName1>
                <Description1>Lash out with stream of shattered glass, or hold for an arcing strike.</Description1>
            </Ability>
            <Ability>
                <AName2>Splinter Storm</AName2>
                <Description2>Gara's armor splinters into a maelstrom of shattered glass that slices enemies and impairs
                    their weapons. Allies who contact the cloud are fortified against damage.
                </Description2>
            </Ability>
            <Ability>
                <AName3>Spectrorage</AName3>
                <Description3>Trap enemies in a carousel of mirrors, forcing them to attack visions of their true selves. 
                    Destroyed mirrors damage their attackers, as does the collapse of the carousel.
                </Description3>
            </Ability>
            <Ability>
                <AName4>Mass Vitrify</AName4>
                <Description4>Create an expanding ring of molten glass that slowly crystallizes enemies who enter. 
                    When the expansion is complete, the ring hardens to block weapons fire. 
                    The ring draws extra strength from the health and shields of crystallized enemies. 
                    Use Shattered Lash to smash the ring and send razor-sharp glass flying outward.
                </Description4>
            </Ability>
        </Abilities>
    </Warframe>
</Warframes>
